{
    "subject": "resource/Washington_Avenue_Soldier's_Monument_and_Triangle",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/New_York",
    "human_readable": "The Washington Avenue Soldier's Monument and Triangle is located in New York.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9733296036720276,
            "question": "Where is the Washington Avenue Soldier's Monument and Triangle located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9343661069869995,
            "question": "Is the Washington Avenue Soldier's Monument and Triangle a building?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.900177001953125,
            "question": "What type of monument is the Washington Avenue Soldier's Monument and Triangle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8812054395675659,
            "question": "Who might have erected the Washington Avenue Soldier's Monument and Triangle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8582826256752014,
            "question": "Are there any other landmarks near the Washington Avenue Soldier's Monument and Triangle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8516585230827332,
            "question": "Is there a story associated with the Washington Avenue Soldier's Monument and Triangle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.839974045753479,
            "question": "Can you describe the appearance of the Washington Avenue Soldier's Monument and Triangle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7514286041259766,
            "question": "What is commemorated by the Washington Avenue Soldier's Monument and Triangle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7200980186462402,
            "question": "Does the Washington Avenue Soldier's Monument and Triangle have historical significance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5995291471481323,
            "question": "What is the name of the monument and landmark in New York?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Washington Avenue Soldier's Monument and Triangle is located in New York.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4478_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the Washington Avenue Soldier's Monument and Triangle have historical significance?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4478_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is commemorated by the Washington Avenue Soldier's Monument and Triangle?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4478_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the appearance of the Washington Avenue Soldier's Monument and Triangle?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4478_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4478_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4478_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4478_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4478_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4478_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4478_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4478_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4478_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4478_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4478_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The Washington Avenue Soldier's Monument and Triangle is indeed mentioned to be located at the junction of Washington Avenue and Lafayette Avenue (NY 59) in Suffern, New York, United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information provided mentions the location of the Washington Avenue Soldier's Monument and Triangle, stating it is located in Suffern, New York. Therefore, the statement that The Washington Avenue Soldier's Monument and Triangle is located in New York is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}